{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.5.5","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":882,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":62,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":true,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_8","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"continue_button","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"continue_button","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202063","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202077","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide125703","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_8","continue_button","si202063","si202077"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide125703"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_9","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"continue_button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"continue_button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202195","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202210","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202252","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_9","continue_button_4","si202195","si202210"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202252"}}},{"id":"si176050","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176057","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176065","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176065_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"teaching","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si176076","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176076_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"teacher","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si176948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176952","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176948_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"teaches","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si176123","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176127","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176020q0","for":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176020q0","for":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176157","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176020q0","for":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176020q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide176020","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si176050","si176069","si176080","si176952","si176127","si176144","si176157","si176110"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide176020"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener176037","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The ______ began class.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si176986","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176993","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si177001","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177001_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"builder","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si177012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177012_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"building","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si177420","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177424","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"rebuilt","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si177059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si177063","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176956q1","for":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176956q1","for":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177093","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide176956q1","for":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177046","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177033","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177020","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide176956q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide176956","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si176986","si177005","si177016","si177424","si177063","si177080","si177093","si177046"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide176956"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener176973","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"They __________ the barn.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si177458","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177465","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si177473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177473_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"apology","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si177484","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177484_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"apologize","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si177892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177892_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"apologist","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si177531","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si177535","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177428q2","for":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177552","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177428q2","for":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177565","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177428q2","for":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177518","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide177428q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide177428","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si177458","si177477","si177488","si177896","si177535","si177552","si177565","si177518"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide177428"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener177445","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"He tried to __________ to his friend.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_10","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_5","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202359","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202373","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202282","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_10","Button_5","si202359","si202373"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202282"}}},{"id":"si177930","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177937","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si177945","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177945_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"weakly","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si177956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si177956_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"weakness","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si178364","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"weaken","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si178003","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si178007","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177900q3","for":"Slide177900q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178024","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177900q3","for":"Slide177900q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178037","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide177900q3","for":"Slide177900q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si202412","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide177900q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide177900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si177930","si177949","si177960","si178368","si178007","si178024","si178037","si202412"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide177900"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener177917","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Hiding in a corner, the dog barked _____.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si178402","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178409","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si178417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178417_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"selfishly","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si178428","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178428_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unselfish","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si178836","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178840","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178836_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"selfishness","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si178475","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si178479","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178372q4","for":"Slide178372q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178496","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178372q4","for":"Slide178372q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178372q4","for":"Slide178372q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si202425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide178372q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide178372","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si178402","si178421","si178432","si178840","si178479","si178496","si178509","si202425"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide178372"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener178389","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Giving away all the prize money was a very __________ act.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si178874","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178881","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si178889","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178889_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"possibility","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si178900","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178904","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178900_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"impossibly","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si179308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179308_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"possible","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si178947","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si178951","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178844q5","for":"Slide178844q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178844q5","for":"Slide178844q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si178981","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide178844q5","for":"Slide178844q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si202438","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide178844q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide178844","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si178874","si178893","si178904","si179312","si178951","si178968","si178981","si202438"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide178844"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener178861","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"He's not sure if he'll go to the beach, but it is _____________ .","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si179346","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179353","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si179361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179365","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179361_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unexpected","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si179372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179372_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"expectation","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si179780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179784","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179780_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"expectant","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si179419","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si179423","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179316q6","for":"Slide179316q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179440","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179316q6","for":"Slide179316q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179316q6","for":"Slide179316q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179393","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide179316q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si202451","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide179316q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide179316","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si179346","si179365","si179376","si179784","si179423","si179440","si179453","si202451"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide179316"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener179333","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The player understood the __________ that she would play in Saturday's game.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si179818","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179825","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si179833","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179837","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179833_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"user","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si179844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179848","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179844_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unusable","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si180252","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180256","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180252_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"usefully","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si179891","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si179895","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179788q7","for":"Slide179788q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179788q7","for":"Slide179788q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179925","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide179788q7","for":"Slide179788q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si179878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide179788q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide179788","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si179818","si179837","si179848","si180256","si179895","si179912","si179925","si179878"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide179788"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener179805","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The bad advice they gave was __________.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si180290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180297","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si180305","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180305_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"civilization","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si180316","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180316_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"civilian","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si180724","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180728","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180724_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"civility","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si180363","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si180367","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180260q8","for":"Slide180260q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180384","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180260q8","for":"Slide180260q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180397","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180260q8","for":"Slide180260q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide180260q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide180260","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si180290","si180309","si180320","si180728","si180367","si180384","si180397","si180350"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide180260"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener180277","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"That man treats everyone with respect and _____.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si180762","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180769","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si180777","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180781","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180777_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"socially","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si180788","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"socialize","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si181196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181200","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181196_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sociable","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si180835","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si180839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180732q9","for":"Slide180732q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180732q9","for":"Slide180732q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180869","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide180732q9","for":"Slide180732q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si180822","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide180732q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide180732","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si180762","si180781","si180792","si181200","si180839","si180856","si180869","si180822"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide180732"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener180749","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The two groups do not __________ with one another.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si181234","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181241","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si181249","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181249_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"chemical","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si181260","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181264","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181260_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"chemistry","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si181668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181672","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181668_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"chemist","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si181307","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si181311","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181204q10","for":"Slide181204q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181328","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181204q10","for":"Slide181204q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181341","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181204q10","for":"Slide181204q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181294","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide181204q10"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide181204","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si181234","si181253","si181264","si181672","si181311","si181328","si181341","si181294"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide181204"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener181221","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Joe's mother is a __________.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si181706","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181713","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si181721","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181725","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181721_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"narrator","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si181732","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181732_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"narrative","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si182140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182140_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"narration","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si181779","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si181783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181676q11","for":"Slide181676q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181800","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181676q11","for":"Slide181676q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181813","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide181676q11","for":"Slide181676q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si181766","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide181676q11"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide181676","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si181706","si181725","si181736","si182144","si181783","si181800","si181813","si181766"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide181676"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener181693","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The students read the __________ poem in class.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si182178","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182185","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si182193","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182193_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"satisfied","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si182204","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182208","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182204_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unsatisfied","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si182612","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182612_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"satisfaction","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si182251","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si182255","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182148q12","for":"Slide182148q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182148q12","for":"Slide182148q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182285","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182148q12","for":"Slide182148q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182238","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide182148q12"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide182148","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si182178","si182197","si182208","si182616","si182255","si182272","si182285","si182238"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide182148"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener182165","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"He felt a lot of __________ at the end of the day","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si182650","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182657","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si182665","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182665_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"permissible","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si182676","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182680","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182676_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"permission","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si183084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183088","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183084_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"permissive","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si182723","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si182727","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182620q13","for":"Slide182620q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182744","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182620q13","for":"Slide182620q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182757","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide182620q13","for":"Slide182620q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si182710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide182620q13"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide182620","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si182650","si182669","si182680","si183088","si182727","si182744","si182757","si182710"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide182620"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener182637","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The list of rules explains what actions are __________.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si183122","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183129","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si183137","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183141","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183137_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"original","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si183148","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183152","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183148_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"originate","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si183556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183556_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"originality","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si183195","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si183199","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183092q14","for":"Slide183092q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183092q14","for":"Slide183092q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183229","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183092q14","for":"Slide183092q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183182","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide183092q14"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide183092","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si183122","si183141","si183152","si183560","si183199","si183216","si183229","si183182"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide183092"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener183109","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The artist's paintings show a lot of freshness and _____.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si183594","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183601","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si183609","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183609_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"resubmit","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si183620","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183624","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183620_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"submission","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si184028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184032","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184028_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"submitted","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si183667","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si183671","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183564q15","for":"Slide183564q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183688","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183564q15","for":"Slide183564q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183701","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide183564q15","for":"Slide183564q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si183654","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide183564q15"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide183564","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si183594","si183613","si183624","si184032","si183671","si183688","si183701","si183654"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide183564"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener183581","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Let me know if you would like to __________ your application.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si184066","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184073","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si184081","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184081_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"settler","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si184092","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184096","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184092_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unsettled","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si184500","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184504","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184500_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"settlement","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si184139","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si184143","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184036q16","for":"Slide184036q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184160","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184036q16","for":"Slide184036q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184173","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184036q16","for":"Slide184036q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184126","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide184036q16"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide184036","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si184066","si184085","si184096","si184504","si184143","si184160","si184173","si184126"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide184036"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener184053","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"There is a large __________ by the river, with many houses.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si184538","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184545","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si184553","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184553_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sufficient","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si184564","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184568","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184564_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sufficiency","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si184972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"insufficient","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si184611","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si184615","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184508q17","for":"Slide184508q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184632","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184508q17","for":"Slide184508q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184645","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184508q17","for":"Slide184508q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si184598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide184508q17"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide184508","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si184538","si184557","si184568","si184976","si184615","si184632","si184645","si184598"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide184508"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener184525","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The tiny amount of paint was __________ to cover the large wall, so we left part of it bare.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_11","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_6","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202539","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202552","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202594","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_11","Button_6","si202539","si202552"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202594"}}},{"id":"si185010","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185017","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si185025","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185029","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185025_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"many","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si185036","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185036_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"soon","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si185444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185448","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185444_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"far","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si185083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si185087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184980q18","for":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185104","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184980q18","for":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185117","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide184980q18","for":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185070","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185057","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185044","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide184980q18"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide184980","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si185010","si185029","si185040","si185448","si185087","si185104","si185117","si185070"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide184980"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener184997","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The person ate __________ pieces of bread.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si185482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185489","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si185497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185497_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"despite","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si185508","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185512","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185508_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"also","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si185916","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185920","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185916_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"because","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si185555","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si185559","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185452q19","for":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185576","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185452q19","for":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185452q19","for":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185542","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185516","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185452q19"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide185452","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si185482","si185501","si185512","si185920","si185559","si185576","si185589","si185542"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide185452"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener185469","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The flower grew __________ it was in the sunlight.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si185954","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185961","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si185969","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185973","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185969_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"except","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si185980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185980_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"however","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si186388","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186388_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"until","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si186027","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si186031","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185924q20","for":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186048","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185924q20","for":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186061","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide185924q20","for":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186014","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186001","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si185988","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide185924q20"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide185924","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si185954","si185973","si185984","si186392","si186031","si186048","si186061","si186014"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide185924"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener185941","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The person worked __________ the job was done.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_12","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_7","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202670","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202683","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202725","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_12","Button_7","si202670","si202683"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202725"}}},{"id":"si186426","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186433","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si186441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186441_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"gas","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si186452","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186456","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186452_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"trucks","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si186860","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186864","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186860_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"bread","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si186499","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si186503","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186396q21","for":"Slide186396q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186520","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186396q21","for":"Slide186396q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186396q21","for":"Slide186396q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186486","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide186396q21"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide186396","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si186426","si186445","si186456","si186864","si186503","si186520","si186533","si186486"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide186396"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener186413","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The man went to the grocery store after he went to the gas station because he wanted to buy some __________.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si186898","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186905","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si186913","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186913_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Instead","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si186924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186928","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186924_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Although","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si187332","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187336","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187332_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Unless","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si186971","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si186975","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186868q22","for":"Slide186868q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186992","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186868q22","for":"Slide186868q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187005","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide186868q22","for":"Slide186868q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si186958","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide186868q22"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide186868","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si186898","si186917","si186928","si187336","si186975","si186992","si187005","si186958"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide186868"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener186885","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"_________ we finish the project, we won't be able to start another one.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si187370","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187377","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si187385","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187385_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Apart from","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si187396","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187400","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187396_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"As revealed by","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si187804","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187804_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"As with","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si187443","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si187447","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187340q23","for":"Slide187340q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187464","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187340q23","for":"Slide187340q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187340q23","for":"Slide187340q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187430","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide187340q23"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide187340","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si187370","si187389","si187400","si187808","si187447","si187464","si187477","si187430"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide187340"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener187357","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"_____________ his black eye, he had been in a fight.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si187842","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187849","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si187857","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187861","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187857_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"conversely","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si187868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187872","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187868_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"equally","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si188276","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188280","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188276_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"consequently","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si187915","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si187919","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187812q24","for":"Slide187812q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187812q24","for":"Slide187812q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187949","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide187812q24","for":"Slide187812q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si187902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide187812q24"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide187812","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si187842","si187861","si187872","si188280","si187919","si187936","si187949","si187902"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide187812"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener187829","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The hotel caught on fire and ____________ had to be closed for several months.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si188314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188321","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si188329","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188333","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188329_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"warm","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si188340","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188344","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188340_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"cold","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si188748","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188752","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188748_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"late","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si188387","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si188391","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188284q25","for":"Slide188284q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188284q25","for":"Slide188284q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188284q25","for":"Slide188284q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide188284q25"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide188284","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si188314","si188333","si188344","si188752","si188391","si188408","si188421","si188374"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide188284"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener188301","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Even though the boy wore his jacket, he was __________ when he arrived.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si188786","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188793","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si188801","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188801_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sharp","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si188812","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188816","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188812_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"crooked","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si189220","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189224","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189220_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"wooden","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si188859","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si188863","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188756q26","for":"Slide188756q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188756q26","for":"Slide188756q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188893","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide188756q26","for":"Slide188756q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si188846","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide188756q26"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide188756","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si188786","si188805","si188816","si189224","si188863","si188880","si188893","si188846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide188756"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener188773","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The mouse ran across the __________ floor.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si189258","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189265","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si189273","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189277","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189273_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"he","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si189284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189288","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189284_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Tonya","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si189692","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189696","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189692_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si189331","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si189335","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189228q27","for":"Slide189228q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189352","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189228q27","for":"Slide189228q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189365","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189228q27","for":"Slide189228q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189318","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide189228q27"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide189228","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si189258","si189277","si189288","si189696","si189335","si189352","si189365","si189318"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide189228"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener189245","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Shouting in a voice louder than her friend Cindy's, Tonya asked Joe to unlock the door, but __________ didn't respond.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si189730","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189737","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si189745","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189749","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189745_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"he","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si189756","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189760","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189756_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"she","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si190164","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190168","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190164_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"they","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si189803","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si189807","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189700q28","for":"Slide189700q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189824","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189700q28","for":"Slide189700q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189837","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide189700q28","for":"Slide189700q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si189790","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide189700q28"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide189700","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si189730","si189749","si189760","si190168","si189807","si189824","si189837","si189790"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide189700"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener189717","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Eating more candy than her sister, Mary asked her brother to get more from the store, but ___________ forgot.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si190202","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190209","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si190217","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190221","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190217_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"a lot","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si190228","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190232","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190228_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"more","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si190636","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190640","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190636_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"some","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si190275","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si190279","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190172q29","for":"Slide190172q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190296","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190172q29","for":"Slide190172q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190309","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190172q29","for":"Slide190172q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190262","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide190172q29"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide190172","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si190202","si190221","si190232","si190640","si190279","si190296","si190309","si190262"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide190172"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener190189","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The apple tree, which was planted more than fifty years ago, doesn't have a very large amount of fruit on it, but it does have _________ .","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si190674","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190681","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si190689","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190689_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"unlike","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si190700","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190704","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190700_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"similar to","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si191108","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191112","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191108_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"except","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si190747","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si190751","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190644q30","for":"Slide190644q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190768","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190644q30","for":"Slide190644q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190781","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide190644q30","for":"Slide190644q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si190734","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide190644q30"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide190644","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si190674","si190693","si190704","si191112","si190751","si190768","si190781","si190734"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide190644"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener190661","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"She was a unique writer _______ any others.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si191146","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191153","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si191161","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191161_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"additionally","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si191172","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191176","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191172_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"but","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si191580","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191584","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191580_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"alternatively","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si191219","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si191223","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191116q31","for":"Slide191116q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191240","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191116q31","for":"Slide191116q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191253","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191116q31","for":"Slide191116q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191206","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide191116q31"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide191116","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si191146","si191165","si191176","si191584","si191223","si191240","si191253","si191206"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide191116"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener191133","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"John is a carpenter; ____________, he also owned a home restoration company.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si191618","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191625","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si191633","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191633_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"too","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si191644","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191648","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191644_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"thus","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si192052","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192056","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192052_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"however","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si191691","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si191695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191588q32","for":"Slide191588q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191712","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191588q32","for":"Slide191588q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191725","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide191588q32","for":"Slide191588q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si191678","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide191588q32"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide191588","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si191618","si191637","si191648","si192056","si191695","si191712","si191725","si191678"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide191588"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener191605","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"The manager decided to give the employee a raise based on his excellent performance ____ far.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si192090","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192097","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si192105","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192109","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192105_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Because","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si192116","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192120","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192116_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"In addition to","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si192524","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192528","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192524_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Especially","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si192163","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si192167","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192060q33","for":"Slide192060q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192184","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192060q33","for":"Slide192060q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192197","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192060q33","for":"Slide192060q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192150","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide192060q33"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide192060","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si192090","si192109","si192120","si192528","si192167","si192184","si192197","si192150"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide192060"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener192077","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"__________ the new bike, the man also bought a helmet.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si192562","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192569","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si192577","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192581","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192577_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"rarely","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si192588","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192592","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192588_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"also","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si192996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193000","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192996_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"don't","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si192635","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si192639","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192532q34","for":"Slide192532q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192656","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192532q34","for":"Slide192532q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192669","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide192532q34","for":"Slide192532q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si192622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide192532q34"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide192532","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si192562","si192581","si192592","si193000","si192639","si192656","si192669","si192622"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide192532"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener192549","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Just as birds migrate south for the winter, many whales __________ head for warmer temperatures.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si193034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193041","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si193049","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193053","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193049_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"meanwhile","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si193060","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193064","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193060_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"alternatively","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si193468","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193472","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193468_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"subsequently","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si193107","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si193111","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193004q35","for":"Slide193004q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193128","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193004q35","for":"Slide193004q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193141","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193004q35","for":"Slide193004q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193094","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193004q35"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide193004","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si193034","si193053","si193064","si193472","si193111","si193128","si193141","si193094"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide193004"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener193021","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"I could walk there, or ___________, drive there in my car.","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_13","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_8","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202801","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202814","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202856","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_13","Button_8","si202801","si202814"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202856"}}},{"id":"si193506","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193513","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si193521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193525","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193521_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"jump","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si193532","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193536","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193532_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"rock","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si193940","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193944","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193940_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"cat","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si193579","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si193583","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193476q36","for":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193600","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193476q36","for":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193613","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193476q36","for":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193566","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193553","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193540","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193476q36"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide193476","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si193506","si193525","si193536","si193944","si193583","si193600","si193613","si193566"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide193476"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener193493","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"stone","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si193978","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193985","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si193993","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193997","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si193993_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"kicking","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si194004","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194008","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194004_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"talking","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si194412","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194416","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194412_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"swimming","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si194051","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si194055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193948q37","for":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194072","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193948q37","for":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194085","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide193948q37","for":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194038","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194025","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194012","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide193948q37"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide193948","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si193978","si193997","si194008","si194416","si194055","si194072","si194085","si194038"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide193948"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener193965","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"voice","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si194450","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194457","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si194465","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194469","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194465_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"glass","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si194476","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194480","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194476_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"chair","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si194884","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194888","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194884_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"middle","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si194523","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si194527","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194420q38","for":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194544","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194420q38","for":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194420q38","for":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194510","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194484","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide194420q38"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide194420","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si194450","si194469","si194480","si194888","si194527","si194544","si194557","si194510"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide194420"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener194437","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"center","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_14","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202932","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si202945","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide202987","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_14","Button_9","si202932","si202945"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide202987"}}},{"id":"si194922","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194929","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si194937","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194941","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194937_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"jump up","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si194948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194952","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194948_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"figure out","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si195356","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195360","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195356_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"carry over","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si194995","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si194999","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194892q39","for":"Slide194892q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194892q39","for":"Slide194892q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195029","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide194892q39","for":"Slide194892q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si194982","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide194892q39"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide194892","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si194922","si194941","si194952","si195360","si194999","si195016","si195029","si194982"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide194892"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener194909","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"solve","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si195394","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195401","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si195409","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195413","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195409_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"information","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si195420","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195424","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195420_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"schedule","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si195828","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195828_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"star","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si195467","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si195471","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195364q40","for":"Slide195364q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195488","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195364q40","for":"Slide195364q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195364q40","for":"Slide195364q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195454","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide195364q40"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide195364","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si195394","si195413","si195424","si195832","si195471","si195488","si195501","si195454"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide195364"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener195381","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"data","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si195866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195873","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si195881","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195885","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195881_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"powerful","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si195892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195896","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195892_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"mad","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si196300","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196300_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sleepy","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si195939","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si195943","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195836q41","for":"Slide195836q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195836q41","for":"Slide195836q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195973","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide195836q41","for":"Slide195836q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si195926","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide195836q41"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide195836","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si195866","si195885","si195896","si196304","si195943","si195960","si195973","si195926"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide195836"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener195853","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"strong","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si196338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196345","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si196353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"glad","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si196364","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196364_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"ask","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si196772","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196776","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"run","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si196411","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si196415","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196308q42","for":"Slide196308q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196308q42","for":"Slide196308q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196308q42","for":"Slide196308q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196398","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide196308q42"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide196308","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si196338","si196357","si196368","si196776","si196415","si196432","si196445","si196398"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide196308"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener196325","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"happy","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si196810","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196817","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si196825","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196829","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196825_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"heavy","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si196836","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196840","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196836_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"small","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si197244","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197248","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197244_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"round","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si196883","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si196887","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196780q43","for":"Slide196780q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196904","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196780q43","for":"Slide196780q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196917","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide196780q43","for":"Slide196780q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si196870","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide196780q43"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide196780","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si196810","si196829","si196840","si197248","si196887","si196904","si196917","si196870"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide196780"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener196797","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"tiny","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si197282","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197289","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si197297","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197297_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"freedom","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si197308","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197312","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197308_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"actions","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si197716","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197720","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197716_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"attitude","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si197355","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si197359","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197252q44","for":"Slide197252q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197376","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197252q44","for":"Slide197252q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197252q44","for":"Slide197252q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197342","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide197252q44"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide197252","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si197282","si197301","si197312","si197720","si197359","si197376","si197389","si197342"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide197252"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener197269","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"behavior","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si197754","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197761","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si197769","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197773","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197769_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"invited","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si197780","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197784","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197780_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"applauded","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si198188","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198188_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"obtained","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si197827","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si197831","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197724q45","for":"Slide197724q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197848","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197724q45","for":"Slide197724q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197861","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide197724q45","for":"Slide197724q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si197814","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide197724q45"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide197724","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si197754","si197773","si197784","si198192","si197831","si197848","si197861","si197814"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide197724"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener197741","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"summoned","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si198226","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198233","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198241","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198245","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198241_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"path","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si198252","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198256","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198252_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"home","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si198660","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198664","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198660_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"treat","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si198299","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198303","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198196q46","for":"Slide198196q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198320","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198196q46","for":"Slide198196q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198333","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198196q46","for":"Slide198196q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198286","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide198196q46"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide198196","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si198226","si198245","si198256","si198664","si198303","si198320","si198333","si198286"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide198196"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener198213","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"domestic","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si198698","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198705","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198713","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198717","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198713_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"brace","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si198724","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198728","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198724_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"friendship","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si199132","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199136","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199132_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"small","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si198771","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si198775","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198668q47","for":"Slide198668q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198792","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198668q47","for":"Slide198668q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198805","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide198668q47","for":"Slide198668q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si198758","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide198668q47"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide198668","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si198698","si198717","si198728","si199136","si198775","si198792","si198805","si198758"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide198668"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener198685","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"alliance","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si199170","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199177","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si199185","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199189","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199185_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"speech","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si199196","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199200","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199196_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"figure","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si199604","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199608","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199604_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"effect","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si199243","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si199247","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199140q48","for":"Slide199140q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199264","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199140q48","for":"Slide199140q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199277","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199140q48","for":"Slide199140q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide199140q48"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide199140","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si199170","si199189","si199200","si199608","si199247","si199264","si199277","si199230"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide199140"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener199157","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"diagram","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si199642","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199649","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si199657","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199661","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199657_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"sense","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si199668","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199672","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199668_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"purchase","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si200076","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200076_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"deliver","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si199715","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si199719","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199612q49","for":"Slide199612q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199736","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199612q49","for":"Slide199612q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199749","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide199612q49","for":"Slide199612q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si199702","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide199612q49"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide199612","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si199642","si199661","si199672","si200080","si199719","si199736","si199749","si199702"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide199612"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener199629","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"perceive","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si200114","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200121","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si200129","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200133","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200129_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"person","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si200140","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200144","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200140_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"science","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si200548","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200552","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200548_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"globe","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si200187","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si200191","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200084q50","for":"Slide200084q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200208","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200084q50","for":"Slide200084q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200221","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200084q50","for":"Slide200084q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200174","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide200084q50"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide200084","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si200114","si200133","si200144","si200552","si200191","si200208","si200221","si200174"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide200084"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener200101","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"biography","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si200586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200593","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si200601","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200605","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200601_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"terrific","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si200612","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200616","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200612_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fortunate","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si201020","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201024","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201020_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"important","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si200659","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si200663","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200556q51","for":"Slide200556q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200680","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200556q51","for":"Slide200556q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide200556q51","for":"Slide200556q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si200646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide200556q51"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide200556","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si200586","si200605","si200616","si201024","si200663","si200680","si200693","si200646"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide200556"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener200573","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"critical","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si201058","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201065","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si201073","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201077","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201073_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"inept","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si201084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201088","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201084_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"illicit","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si201492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201496","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201492_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"weary","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si201131","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si201135","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201028q52","for":"Slide201028q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201152","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201028q52","for":"Slide201028q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201165","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201028q52","for":"Slide201028q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201118","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide201028q52"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide201028","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si201058","si201077","si201088","si201496","si201135","si201152","si201165","si201118"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide201028"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener201045","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"fatigue","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si201530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201537","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si201545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201549","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201545_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"clarify","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si201556","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201560","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201556_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"expel","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si201964","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201964_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"instruct","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si201603","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si201607","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201500q53","for":"Slide201500q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201624","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201500q53","for":"Slide201500q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201637","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide201500q53","for":"Slide201500q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si201590","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide201500q53"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide201500","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si201530","si201549","si201560","si201968","si201607","si201624","si201637","si201590"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":3},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide201500"},"question":{"interactionId":"Screener201517","quizId":379,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"elaborate","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si176183","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176190","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176194","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176198","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176202","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176206","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176210","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176214","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176218","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176226","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176230","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176234","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si176284","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176242","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176259","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176272","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si176238","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide176169","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide176169"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"SARA screener","class":"project","title":"SARA screener","children":["Slide125703","Slide202252","Slide176020","Slide176956","Slide177428","Slide202282","Slide177900","Slide178372","Slide178844","Slide179316","Slide179788","Slide180260","Slide180732","Slide181204","Slide181676","Slide182148","Slide182620","Slide183092","Slide183564","Slide184036","Slide184508","Slide202594","Slide184980","Slide185452","Slide185924","Slide202725","Slide186396","Slide186868","Slide187340","Slide187812","Slide188284","Slide188756","Slide189228","Slide189700","Slide190172","Slide190644","Slide191116","Slide191588","Slide192060","Slide192532","Slide193004","Slide202856","Slide193476","Slide193948","Slide194420","Slide202987","Slide194892","Slide195364","Slide195836","Slide196308","Slide196780","Slide197252","Slide197724","Slide198196","Slide198668","Slide199140","Slide199612","Slide200084","Slide200556","Slide201028","Slide201500","Slide176169"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide176020q0","Slide176956q1","Slide177428q2","Slide177900q3","Slide178372q4","Slide178844q5","Slide179316q6","Slide179788q7","Slide180260q8","Slide180732q9","Slide181204q10","Slide181676q11","Slide182148q12","Slide182620q13","Slide183092q14","Slide183564q15","Slide184036q16","Slide184508q17","Slide184980q18","Slide185452q19","Slide185924q20","Slide186396q21","Slide186868q22","Slide187340q23","Slide187812q24","Slide188284q25","Slide188756q26","Slide189228q27","Slide189700q28","Slide190172q29","Slide190644q30","Slide191116q31","Slide191588q32","Slide192060q33","Slide192532q34","Slide193004q35","Slide193476q36","Slide193948q37","Slide194420q38","Slide194892q39","Slide195364q40","Slide195836q41","Slide196308q42","Slide196780q43","Slide197252q44","Slide197724q45","Slide198196q46","Slide198668q47","Slide199140q48","Slide199612q49","Slide200084q50","Slide200556q51","Slide201028q52","Slide201500q53"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":54,"passScore":44}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide125703","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide202252","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide176020","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide176956","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide177428","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide202282","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide177900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide178372","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide178844","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide179316","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide179788","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide180260","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide180732","title":"Slide 13"},{"id":"Slide181204","title":"Slide 14"},{"id":"Slide181676","title":"Slide 15"},{"id":"Slide182148","title":"Slide 16"},{"id":"Slide182620","title":"Slide 17"},{"id":"Slide183092","title":"Slide 18"},{"id":"Slide183564","title":"Slide 19"},{"id":"Slide184036","title":"Slide 20"},{"id":"Slide184508","title":"Slide 21"},{"id":"Slide202594","title":"Slide 22"},{"id":"Slide184980","title":"Slide 23"},{"id":"Slide185452","title":"Slide 24"},{"id":"Slide185924","title":"Slide 25"},{"id":"Slide202725","title":"Slide 26"},{"id":"Slide186396","title":"Slide 27"},{"id":"Slide186868","title":"Slide 28"},{"id":"Slide187340","title":"Slide 29"},{"id":"Slide187812","title":"Slide 30"},{"id":"Slide188284","title":"Slide 31"},{"id":"Slide188756","title":"Slide 32"},{"id":"Slide189228","title":"Slide 33"},{"id":"Slide189700","title":"Slide 34"},{"id":"Slide190172","title":"Slide 35"},{"id":"Slide190644","title":"Slide 36"},{"id":"Slide191116","title":"Slide 37"},{"id":"Slide191588","title":"Slide 38"},{"id":"Slide192060","title":"Slide 39"},{"id":"Slide192532","title":"Slide 40"},{"id":"Slide193004","title":"Slide 41"},{"id":"Slide202856","title":"Slide 42"},{"id":"Slide193476","title":"Slide 43"},{"id":"Slide193948","title":"Slide 44"},{"id":"Slide194420","title":"Slide 45"},{"id":"Slide202987","title":"Slide 46"},{"id":"Slide194892","title":"Slide 47"},{"id":"Slide195364","title":"Slide 48"},{"id":"Slide195836","title":"Slide 49"},{"id":"Slide196308","title":"Slide 50"},{"id":"Slide196780","title":"Slide 51"},{"id":"Slide197252","title":"Slide 52"},{"id":"Slide197724","title":"Slide 53"},{"id":"Slide198196","title":"Slide 54"},{"id":"Slide198668","title":"Slide 55"},{"id":"Slide199140","title":"Slide 56"},{"id":"Slide199612","title":"Slide 57"},{"id":"Slide200084","title":"Slide 58"},{"id":"Slide200556","title":"Slide 59"},{"id":"Slide201028","title":"Slide 60"},{"id":"Slide201500","title":"Slide 61"},{"id":"Slide176169","title":"Slide 62"}]}